{"data":[{"question":"The strongest dump trucks work in rock quarries, ________ tons of rocks and soil at one time.","a":"that they move","b":"they move","c":"where they move","d":"which they move","answer":"3","explain":"\n- In rock quarries: implies the place - where.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Alice Freeman, ________ to head Wellesley College at age 27, is one of the youngest college presidents in history.","a":"who was appointed","b":"has been appointed","c":"that is appointed","d":"is appointed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (at age 27).\u00a0\n- Alice Freeman: implies person- who.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Helen Keller lost both her sight and hearing after a severe illness ________.","a":"of her age in 19 months","b":"she was 19 months old","c":"when she was 19 months old","d":"when 19 months old she was","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Refer to age: at the age of + number\/ to be + number + year(s)\/month(s) old.\u00a0\n- When\/ while + S+ V + O\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Because aluminum is lighter and cheaper ________, it is frequently used for high-tension power transmission.","a":"as copper","b":"than copper","c":"for copper","d":"more copper","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the comparative form of short adjectives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"It is only recently that ballets have been based on themes ________ American life.","a":"reflecting","b":"reflects","c":"is reflecting","d":"reflected","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun.\u00a0\n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle.\u00a0\n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Poison oak generates irritating poisons ________ even if people merely brush against the plants.","a":"they can affect people","b":"that can affect people","c":"what can effect people","d":"which do they affect","answer":"2","explain":"\n- That : That introduces essential clauses while \"which, what\" introduces nonessential clauses.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"________ ants live in colonies, keep farms, go to war, carry off slaves, and have a society somewhat like human beings.","a":"Studies of ant life show that","b":"Studies of ant life that","c":"That is studied","d":"That the studies of ant life","answer":"1","explain":"\n- S + show that + Clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Generic medications are just as ________, and much less expensive.","a":"effectively brand-name products","b":"brand-name products effective","c":"brand-name products as effective","d":"effective as brand-name products","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Comparison of Equality: as + adj\/ adv+ as.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"________ is no way to tell the exact number of heroin addicts in the United States.","a":"It","b":"There","c":"What","d":"Each","answer":"2","explain":"- There is no way to do something\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Ernest Hemingway is ________ of modern fiction.","a":"one of the molders","b":"the molders one","c":"who is one of the molders","d":"the molders who is the one","answer":"1","explain":"\n- One of the (superlative adj)+ plural noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}